ELIZABETH ADAMS

Client Services Manager

Fort Worth, TX 76116

lizzyadams@sbcglobal.net

817.917.5214

Client Services Manager with a over 10 years of experience in customer service and microsoft suite. The ability to learn new skills while performing duties in a safe manner. Proficiency in Microsoft suite. Experience in Operations Management and business analyst of a digital agency

- Business Analyst Customer Service Leadership
 - Excel Google Sheets Microsoft Office Suite



WORK EXPERIENCE

Client Services Manager

Digital Connect Group - Fort Worth, TX

December 2015 to Present

- · Perform daily account management for current and potential clients through a robust CRM
- Operations management in a fast paced environment
- Digital Marketing tasks through Google Ads and Facebook Ads
- Manage and maintain updates for large keyword lists.
- Provide creative copy suggestions and graphical ad terms for my technology associate. This is in regards to search engine optimization
- Maintain company websites
- Review data from various analytics platforms and refine marketing strategy
- Generate weekly and monthly client reporting for all major metrics, goals tracking, revenue tracking, and other paid search initiatives.

Level 3 Hairstylist

TONI & GUY - Southlake, TX

November 2012 to December 2015

- Consulting with clients on stylistic options for their hair.
- Listening to client needs to determine their preferences.
- Describing different hair care products and their benefits.
- Shampooing, cutting, coloring and highlighting hair.
- Acting as salespersons to sell clients hair care retail products.
- Adhering to salon safety and cleanliness standards.
- Keeping updated on hairstyle trends and styling methods

Customer Service Representative

DON DAVIS NISSAN - Arlington, TX

February 2006 to November 2009

- Build monthly spread sheets
- Make/Answer phone calls
- Deliver exceptional customer service

Unit Secretary

MEDICAL CENTER OF ARLINGTON - Arlington, TX

August 2005 to January 2006

- · Build client charts
- Make/Answer phone calls
- Deliver exceptional customer service



EDUCATION

Associates in Fine Arts in Fine Arts

Tarrant County College 2018



SKILLS

- Client Service
- Customer Service
- Mailing
- Home Health
- Home Care
- Homecare



ASSESSMENTS

Supervisory Skills: Directing Others — Proficient

August 2019

Motivating others through feedback to identify improvements or corrective actions.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share assignment/qdlj-k0x7dc22myk

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.